The one thing that made
the United States
so dangerous for so long
was that your people believed
in the fantasy of freedom.
Spare me the fucking lectures
on failed societies.
How bad can
this fucking thing get?
SVR has some knowledge
of the Lioness program,
but they don't have
definitive proof.
Joe can provide that.
Okay, NSA has a hit.
All right, he's in a hangar
right fucking here.
-Can you put us on the roof?
-You got a bird?
-Down, down, down, down, down!
-Down now! Down now!
-Fuck.
-Bobby.
Blood on the floor?
Looks like you missed a spot,
motherfucker!
We have diplomatic immunity.
-Tail number.
-N, five...
Departed 11:07.
They loaded her
onto a Challenger 300.
She's on a jet.
Destination unknown,
transponder disabled.
We're still a step behind,
and time's not on our side.
♪ 'Cause it be me poppin' out,
shittin' on these hos ♪
♪ It be me, my body tea,
I'm bitches' goals, look ♪
♪ It be me with my skin
glowin' in the sun ♪
Would you like a dance?
♪ I'll tell a nigga ♪
♪ His mama raised a bum, yeah ♪
♪ It be me just lookin' perfect,
head to toe, look ♪
♪ It be you out here just
lookin' regular ho... ♪
I think I said
it earlier, and I meant it.
-You are the prett...
-Are you gonna tell me
-I'm the prettiest girl?
-You are...
How'd you know?
I wish I could take you home.
You can.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. Just got to sign me out.
-Okay.
-Yeah?
Yeah.
-Wait here.
-Okay.
Just gonna get my things.
♪ Fifty inches
to my butt, yeah ♪
♪ He on my phone... ♪
I'll stay right here.
Hurry back.
♪ Stressin' over niggas ♪
♪ You lookin' for him, he
right here under my pictures ♪
♪ I'm turnt up at the party,
I'm geekin' out my body ♪
♪ She shake it, clap it for me,
these bitches love some Cardi ♪
♪ I'm turnt up at the party,
I'm geekin' out my body ♪
♪ She twerk it, clap it for me,
like yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Hello, it's me,
hello, it's me ♪
♪ Hello, it's me... ♪
Ready for me?
♪ Hello, it's me ♪
♪ Hello, it's me,
hello, it's me ♪
♪ It be me
that's getting tricked on ♪
♪ By somebody's baby dad ♪
♪ It be me that's lookin' sexy ♪
♪ It be me that's lookin' cute ♪
♪ It be me with body bustin' out
this Miu Miu bodysuit ♪
♪ It be me... ♪
Right and left thumb.
Damn. Y'all take this
pretty serious.
♪ With all that motion,
havin' shit that's goin' on ♪
♪ It ain't me ♪
♪ It's not my fault me
and broke hos don't get along ♪
♪ Hey, I'm turnt up
at the party ♪
♪ I'm geekin' out my body... ♪
That it?
Need a fucking blood sample
or anything?
Huh?
I'll just... Okay.
See you tomorrow.
♪ It's me, hello, it's me ♪
♪ I'm that bitch, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Hello, it's me,
hello, it's me ♪
♪ Hello, it's me ♪
♪ It's that bitch, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ "Ivory"
by The Movement playing ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
♪ Used to think about you... ♪
Uh-huh.
♪ What I give you... ♪
Where's your bedroom?
That way.
♪ Not as if you had enough... ♪
You have really good taste.
Oh. I can't take credit.
My company owns this apartment.
Your company has
really good taste.
♪ He won't give you... ♪
♪ I couldn't tell
what you want anymore ♪
♪ How to cold you,
craving, used to... ♪
♪ 'Cause I never felt you... ♪
It's your lucky day.
You ain't fucking kidding.
♪ I never felt you, oh ♪
♪ Now the vision of the new ♪
♪ And you say ♪
♪ Oh, you ♪
♪ To feel... ♪
Hey! What the fuck?
Our thoughts exactly.
What the fuck, Cade?
What the fuck
would motivate the son
of two anesthesiologists
who went to Georgetown,
who grew up with every
possible advantage in life
to take money
from a foreign agent?
More specifically,
what did you sell them?
What trade secret
of Booz Allen's
did you fucking sell them?
I want a lawyer.
I would, too,
if we were the FBI.
But we aren't.
I'm here to get the name
and the contact information
of your handler,
or my associate over here is
gonna carry you out the patio,
and he's gonna throw you
off the fucking building.
What the fuck
are you talking about? Wait.
Jesus Christ!
Hey, no, wait. Okay.
Ah, all right. Wait! Okay, hey!
What, you-you got
something to say?
My phone.
A name, Cade.
-Rooster. It's under Rooster.
-Rooster.
What does that mean, "you got
something"? What do you got?
It just depends
on-on whatever he's looking for.
He, who is he?
Is it Rooster?
Who the fuck is Rooster?
-I don't know.
-Cut the fucking bullshit.
-What does he look like?
Like a fucking math nerd.
Set him down.
Fuck.
How did you meet Rooster?
He gave me a test.
-A test?
-The answers to a data
structures and algorithms test.
Gave 'em to me and fucking
now I don't have a choice.
Do you understand me?
I don't get money.
He owns my fucking degree,
my whole future.
Do you get it? My whole future.
Not anymore, he doesn't.
We hold it now.
So you get something.
You send him a text,
he sends you an address, and
you meet him there, is that it?
Yes.
Get dressed.
Okay.
Do you have a coffee machine
in your kitchen?
-Huh?
-A coffee maker.
Fuck, Cade.
-Yeah.
-Can someone figure out coffee?
Our meet is at 0800.
Am I on coffee duty?
If the shoe fits, baby.
Since when did I become
Sally fucking Homemaker?
Tucker...
You want to explain
to Cade who we are?
"Shut the fuck up"
is who we are.
Not another fucking word,
-you understand me?
-Yes. I understand...
The fuck did I just say?
That's who we are.
Have a seat, Richard.
Uh...
Shyla didn't mention
a boyfriend.
All right?
Did you mention a wife?
Um...
Slipped my mind.
Four children.
You got me, man.
You-you got me.
Yes. I do.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh.
There's also video,
two hours of it.
Well...
That Viagra's no joke.
What can I say?
This is funny to you, huh?
There's
a certain irony to it.
Yes.
I see no irony.
Hands, hands, hands, hands!
Hey!
-You see it now, don't you?
-Hands!
Turn the fuck around. Face down.
Hands behind your head.
Interlock your fingers.
Now, lower your head down
to your knees.
Head all the way down.
Don't move.
Stand up. Turn around.
Hands behind your head.
Why me? I don't got shit
to do with this.
Don't bullshit a bullshitter.
Get the fuck up. Get up!
What the fuck?
I have rights!
No, you don't. Not anymore.
I hope you wore
a fucking condom.
I'm serious.
I hope you wore it, too.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
you really fucked that stripper?
Hey, I'm a method actor,
okay, bro?
You Ground Branch guys
are fucking nuts.
Oh, okay, we're nuts?
Okay, got it.
New deal on the way.
Check your Signal.
Yes, ma'am. Coming our way when?
You're already late.
Yes, ma'am.
This kid's gonna pass out.
He needs to calm
the fuck down. Tell him.
I'm trying.
Are Bravo and Charlie in place?
Bravo, Charlie, this is Alpha.
Are you set?
-Bravo set.
-Charlie set.
Good to go.
Asset's in place.
Why are you sweating?
Hungover as fuck.
This didn't need
to happen today.
I don't like
having all this shit on a drive.
Green light.
Green light, let's go.
Bravo, Charlie, you are green.
What the fuck?!
Eyes down.
Okay. Okay, okay.
You didn't think
this was over, did you?
We're just getting started.
You can't hold me.
My student visa gives me
diplomatic immunity.
That's why you kids
have got to stop
getting your news from TikTok.
Only diplomats
who are registered with
the U.S. Department of State
are granted diplomatic immunity.
You're not on that list.
Believe me. We checked.
So, you're gonna be charged
with 18 U.S. Code 1831
and 18 U.S.C. 793-794.
I-I don't know what those mean.
Well, your lawyer's
gonna explain it
when you get one.
Now, let me
tell you the penalty.
When you're found guilty,
which you will be, because
there's caught red-handed
and caught with
your dick in your hand,
and, somehow,
you found a way to do both.
And we have it on video.
Let me get back to the penalty,
which is life imprisonment
times three,
a maximum-security prison
based on your threat
to national security.
Can you imagine the commodity
a handsome young man
who can't weigh more
than a buck 50
would be to a bunch
of drug traffickers
who have surrendered to the fact
that they will never
get to love a woman again?
This is my senior case officer.
And she?
She's gonna determine whether
you can provide us
with enough information
that we're gonna pause
our demand for justice.
And when I say justice,
I mean vindictive retribution.
Understand the game?
I think so.
Trade information for freedom.
No.
We're not trading anything.
You're gonna dazzle me
with hard data, names,
and explicit information
to the structure, financing,
and execution
of all your operations.
I'm gonna need to understand
your flow of information
as well as you do.
Or...
I'm gonna drive
to the county jail
with a stack of 100s
as thick as my fucking neck.
And I'll spend
the next six hours
cherry-picking your cellmate
for the evening.
And then, tomorrow,
we get to do it all over again.
So what are all you
Belarus fuckers
doing running around
Washington, D.C.?
I'm Lithuanian.
Your passport's Lithuanian.
But last I checked,
Belarus military
wasn't allowing Lithuanians
in their military.
I've never been to Belarus.
I don't know Belarus.
Boy, you got to give me a
little more fucking credit here.
I'm a senior case officer
for the CIA,
so if I want data on someone,
I just take their fingerprints
from their visa application,
and I run it through
a little program at the NSA,
which cross-references those
fingerprints with Interpol,
EU Entry, Privium, ETAS,
not to mention the database
of military enrollment
in virtually every nation,
if it pays a pension or has
a Veterans Affairs Department,
which...
our little brainiacs
have been mining and stealing
data from since the...
the internet went live.
You joined in 2010,
accepted to SSU in 2012,
served in
the 5th Spetsnaz Brigade,
where you participated
in putting down
the 2020 uprising in Brest,
where you guys...
you guys just started
smoking fuckers.
Wow.
I mean, that...
that must really simplify
dispersing protesters.
As a foreign national
entering the U.S.
on a fraudulent passport
and engaging in espionage...
which is a big no-no
around here...
the constitutional protections
that lawful visitors,
immigrants, and citizens enjoy,
they don't apply to you.
So, I'm not gonna sit here and
listen to your memorized lies
and your bullshit intel that
you're gonna try and float me.
What I am gonna do is I'm gonna
send you to Guantánamo Bay.
Stick you in an eight-by-eight
cage, no ceiling,
feed you three times a week,
while you cook
in the fucking heat,
and we blast Metallica
at 110 decibels
24 hours a fucking day
for three years.
Then we'll see if you feel like
telling me the truth.
Hey.
You ever had dengue fever?
You're gonna love it.
Yeah, the locals call it
"bone-break fever"
because I guess
that's what it feels like.
It's not a matter of
if you get it, I promise you,
I promise you,
you're gonna get it,
'cause it's the first thing
we give you.
Have a good trip.
We'll see you in 2028.
Get up. Up.
Wait. Wait. Wait!
I will tell you the truth!
I will tell you now!
I promise I will tell you
the truth!
I will tell you now.
All right, guys,
bring him back in.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Don't go far, guys.
Hey.
I want to introduce you
to somebody.
What do you think of that, huh?
A fucking Russian
double agent in the flesh.
I mean, you just...
Jesus, you just don't see that
every day, do you?
What do you think it means
that I told you who she is?
It means...
I'm never going free.
Ever.
All we do today
is pick a prison.
And believe me
when I tell you...
there are levels to that game.
They're five minutes out.
-That was them?
-Mm-hmm.
Kaitlyn, would you care
to bring us up to speed?
Sure. Um, we began our operation
targeting known assets
of Russian intelligence.
We have apprehended
four individuals in one sting,
two individuals in another,
although,
the second appears
to be an asset
of the Chinese
Ministry of State.
Um, our two senior case officers
are meant to be here now.
They're, um,
conducting interviews
and they're en route to debrief.
NSA has been processing
the information provided.
They're also
mining information from
seized computers
and cell phones,
and NSA is sending information
in real time as they gather it.
Director Westfield, would you
care to elaborate on CIA's
decision to completely exclude
FBI's counterintelligence
from this operation?
All our officers
have FBI credentials, ma'am.
This was, in essence,
a CED operation.
Okay. Without any oversight,
without any adherence
to the chain of command.
So, in other words,
this operation
was and is complete bullshit.
And those credentials are
a convenient work-around
to avoid violating
the National Security Act
of 1947
and Executive Act 12333,
which you still violated.
Okay. Number one,
CED was informed
once the targets were detained
and are in FBI custody
as we speak.
Oh, yeah? All of them?
Two are still being interviewed.
Mm.
Are any of my agents
present at those interviews?
Sworn agents of the FBI
are present, yes.
No, I don't mean your agents.
I mean my agents.
Can we pause the dick-measuring
over jurisdiction here
and discuss what has been
uncovered thus far, okay?
If this procedure
is not followed to the letter,
those cases
will not be prosecutable.
I couldn't give a shit
about prosecution.
I care about what secrets
have been stolen,
who has those secrets,
is our national security
compromised
and to what extent?
Crimes against national security
give us extreme latitude
in detaining individuals,
as they are essentially
war crimes,
which suspends
the due process clause,
as well as
the search and seizure
protections
of the Fourth Amendment.
We can detain them
for years without trial.
If we assess that they are
a continued threat
to national security,
we can detain them indefinitely.
That is why I don't care
about prosecution.
Which brings us to the question:
is our national security
at risk?
Without a question.
Give us an example.
So, my Lioness was in contact
with a software engineer
at a leading defense firm
with heavy focus
on AI enhancement.
This individual was extorted by
a Chinese Ministry of State
contract agent
into providing sensitive,
privileged information
on multiple occasions.
NSA is processing
the exposed data
to make a threat
and damage assessment.
What's most concerning
is this agent
seems to have been activated
by a professor at a university
where both these individuals
obtained advanced degrees
in software engineering.
The Chinese agent himself is
a software engineer at Raytheon.
We are in contact
with their head of security,
and he has isolated all
of this individual's accounts
and is processing
with DIA and NSA as we speak.
It appears
a software engineer professor
that taught
both these individuals
is also complicit based on
statements by the detainee.
We have obtained a warrant
through CED,
and we will be picking him up
this afternoon.
Another Chinese national?
American citizen.
A Richard Ealy,
born 9-22-67 in Boston,
undergrad at Cornell,
advanced degrees
in both computer science
and software engineering.
He taught at UM-Ann Arbor until
2018, and then he came here.
And how's he involved?
Apparently,
he provides exam answers
to Mr. Lin... code name Rooster...
which then he peddles down
to students
who seem to lack
a level of moral integrity.
How is this professor
compensated?
Our source says no compensation.
It appears that our professor
believes that our government
and our economic system
are fatally flawed,
and he's more aligned
politically
with the Chinese
governmental structure.
So he's a communist?
Uh, it's hard
to call him a communist
with a professor's salary
of $280,000 a year
and an IT consulting firm,
but he certainly appears to be
a communist sympathizer.
So beyond this professor,
how far does this go?
We'll have
a better understanding
after I interview him.
What we learned in Afghanistan
is those motivated
by ideology never cooperate.
With all due respect, ma'am,
but what we've learned
in Afghanistan
is those motivated by religion
never cooperate
because their god
is with them everywhere...
in prison, in exile,
and in death.
Ideology is useless
in those places.
Besides, he's got
a wife and two kids...
both of them in private school...
and a beach house
in Hilton Head.
It looks like his ideology
remains on campus.
Anything else?
More tomorrow, I hope.
So we placed
an operator undercover,
posed as a salesman
for a defense contractor,
placed him in a bar
known for honeypotting,
and by the end of the night,
he made contact
and provided necessary evidence
to convince Russian
foreign agents to move on him.
What was
the evidence, if I may ask?
Well, typically...
these honeypotters
perform sexual acts
on the subjects,
providing blackmail material
that allows them
to be subjugated by the agent,
forcing them to provide intel
in any number of forms.
Are you saying
that your operator
allowed sexual acts
to be performed on him?
If I recall from the video,
my operator did most
of the performing, ma'am.
Okay, so this has gone
completely rogue.
Look, okay,
with-with all due respect,
we are not infiltrating
some biker gang
selling stolen guns and speed.
These are enemies of the state
actively seeking means
to weaken us as a nation.
We broke no laws.
Two consenting adults had sex,
no money exchanged hands.
All right? The-the fact that
one of them did so
with the intent of extorting
one of my officers,
that's a crime, and one
you should charge her with.
Oh, and by the way, you can slap
a treason charge on top of it.
You're welcome.
Okay, I could do
without the flippancy.
Yeah, and I can do without
the inference of impropriety
towards my officers
at every fucking turn.
Oh, can we stop
the dick-measuring
of jurisdiction and procedure?
Kyle, please continue.
Okay. Well...
what's interesting
is these Russians
all have Belarus citizenship,
using passports
in Lithuania, Latvia, Malta.
Also, the senior contract agent
fed me intel,
which was all planted.
How do you know
this information was planted?
Because it all checks out.
Everything he gave me,
NSA can verify,
which means, obviously,
we already knew it.
And our double agent verified
that these gives
are all standard offerings that
most Russian agents
would utilize if detained.
So, we are gonna
send him to Gitmo,
let him cook for a bit
and see if his intel improves.
Do you feel the Belarus agents
are, um,
con-connected to, um,
Russian forces directly
or indirectly?
My best guess?
They're guns for hire,
seeking information valuable
to our adversaries...
Qatar, Syria, Iran,
Venezuela,
possibly China, but doubtful,
since Russia sees China
as an adversary as well.
So, beyond picking up
this professor,
what's the next steps?
This was a pretty splashy
first day.
They know we're hunting,
which was the goal.
They'll clam up.
Their sources will get nervous.
They'll possibly even reach out
to us looking for a parachute.
We have a very strong list
of Russian sources in the U.S.
-Hmm.
-NSA has already dug
into their bank accounts
and found some very big,
big-ticket purchases
that don't necessarily align
with their income.
Most of these sources
are U.S. citizens,
so they'll be coming your way,
Director Wexler.
Okay, so why not this professor?
Let us take it from here.
We have a latitude
in questioning
that the FBI does not have.
Because we're not
investigating a crime,
nor can we charge him with any,
we're simply seeking information
in the interest
of national security.
So, no Miranda rights,
no Fourth, Fifth, and 14th
to limit the scope
or manner of our inquiries.
And certainly,
anything that we uncover
will still be admissible
in court
as witness testimony
on our part.
All right.
Good work, Joe.
Stay with it.
Uh, one last thing.
What we're about to divulge
requires, uh, T.S. clearance.
It is Yankee White only.
Uh, Kaityln, Kyle and I don't
have that clearance.
You don't need it. You're
the ones who mine the intel.
We have a source
in the Russian SVR.
This individual has provided us
with a list of Russian sources
who are currently working
in the U.S.
We're aware.
Uh, what you aren't aware of
is some of the more prominent
names on that list.
How prominent?
Executives at multiple
television networks.
Senior editors
at The Post and The Times.
Four district court judges,
two circuit court judges.
Seven members of the House
and two in the Senate.
My God.
But you know this?
Not speculate, know it?
-We...
-We have the SVR files, ma'am,
which contain
bank account information,
routing numbers, pay schedules
through various foundations
and NGOs, typically
as campaign contributions.
The evidence is damning.
The question is...
what would you
like us to do with it?
Our worry is that,
whether we detain
or FBI arrests,
this is gonna send a shock wave
through the higher learning
institutions,
through the major media outlets,
through the public officials,
both elected to office.
Will it cause a collapse
in confidence
through these institutions
that is actually more helpful
to the Russians
than the sources
they have in place?
We could do arrests in stages
over a period of time.
What period of time
are we talking about?
Once one of the dominoes falls,
they all fall,
whether we knock
them down or not.
May I?
Joe, let us figure this out.
Well, I know.
I just...
No, I'd...
I'd like to hear
what she has to say.
Go ahead, Joe.
Look, Kyle and I are the
only spies in the room, right?
It was spies
who hooked these fish.
You can arrest them, sure,
but we can switch the hooks.
Remove theirs, put in ours.
Explain that.
We approach
every compromised official,
we present them our evidence,
and we give them
the option of retiring
in the next 24 hours
or they face prison.
We don't offer them immunity.
We don't offer them anything.
We simply withhold action.
They tell us everything,
they give us everything,
and from this day forward,
they are our sources.
Who are these senators?
Olson and Mayer.
Mayer's a freshman.
It's likely they had him before
and were just instrumental
in his decision to run.
We audited
his campaign contributions:
energy company in Crimea,
Armenian IT company,
Alibaba, Tencent, Baidu.
Jesus.
Yes.
Well, your plan
makes sense, Joe.
They're removed
from power immediately.
They have no means
of defying the demand,
because we can prosecute.
We'd be forced to,
in this instance.
No statute of limitations
on treason.
We could prosecute
any time we see fit.
Okay, you two.
You take Mayer, I'll take Olson.
Yes, sir.
You two,
start working the House.
With pleasure.
Director Wexler.
-Sir?
-If we can have
special agents from CED
at all of these meetings.
Anyone that says no is arrested.
Let the chips fall
where they may.
God have mercy on us all.
Do you think your guys
were connected
with the guys in my house?
How many contract agents
from Belarus
can there be in D.C., right?
They got to be.
Before you ship
your guy off, ask, push.
My guy ain't talking,
not for a few months anyway.
Just ask anyway. Plant the seed
before you stick him in a box.
It'll be the thing
he trades to get out.
All right. I'll ask him.
Have fun with your professor.
I plan to.
How's our houseguest?
Pretty quiet,
except for your big prize.
Yeah? What's he saying?
Been praying.
Lot of good
that's gonna do him.
He's been praying in Arabic.
Ah, you got to be shitting me.
They all going to Gitmo?
No, just the prize.
You guys ready to travel?
We have a Moose holding for us
out at Andrews.
Wheels up at 1900, though.
This won't take long.
Well...
you've been holding out on me.
Didn't realize you were
a religious man.
Been listening to you
"Allahu Akbar"
for the last couple hours.
You a Lipka Tatar? Huh?
That's not very Muslim of you,
helping the Russian state.
The enemy of my enemy
is my friend.
Ah... Okay.
Now we're getting somewhere.
All right, well, listen,
you're about to ship off
to Camp Hell in a few minutes.
So, while you're there,
sitting in the 100-degree heat,
buck naked
with about a thousand mosquitoes
the size of fucking sparrows
sucking you dry...
I want you to think about this.
Two Belarus contract agents
made an abduction attempt
on a case officer in Virginia.
You know what I'm referring to?
-This is news to me.
-Oh, come on.
Give me a fucking break.
You got less than 40,000 people
in your entire fucking army,
a few hundred in SF.
All you fuckers know each other,
and you know exactly
what I'm talking about.
But...
when you feel like talking,
just tell that
marine sergeant who
beats you with a baton
before every meal.
'Cause that's how you make
the pain stop, Alex.
And it's the only way.
Get up. Get up.
What is paramount to understand:
AI will likely render what I do
and what you aspire to do
as obsolete.
Likewise
to careers in marketing,
accounting, engineering...
whether software,
biological, mechanical...
data analysis,
research management.
All of these careers will
disappear in the next decade.
You must alter the focus
of your education to include
machine learning,
computer vision
and management strategies,
NLP engineering,
computer vision engineering.
And you must prepare yourselves
for a world
in which your endeavors
are not compensated with money.
Your compensation is
in the collective betterment
of our society, of our state.
What, no money, you say?
Yep, that's the future.
Your efforts will be compensated
through the services provided to
you in return from the state...
housing, health care, food,
clean transportation, entertainment.
And as you prepare yourselves
for a career in the future,
you must prepare yourselves
also for a world
that replaces
the imperialist goals
and economic meddling
of a "free-market society"
with a dedication to a state
that in turn dedicates itself
to an equitable life
for all humankind.
Interesting position.
It's not a position,
it's the inevitable truth.
Let's say the inevitable
becomes true tomorrow.
Are you willing to pull
your kids out of private school,
turn your beach house over
to the government,
and allow them to seize
the four million in equities
Fidelity manages for you?
I bet not.
You strike me more as a
"have your cake and eat it, too"
kind of guy.
Who are you?
I...
am the inevitable consequence
of your actions, Mr. Ealy.
And what actions
would you be referring to?
Selling exam answers
through your TA to students
with the intent to extort
and recruit them
to provide information
to the Chinese Ministry
of State Security.
The legal definition
for that action
is treason, Mr. Ealy.
I guess you'll be
surrendering your money
and your property to
the U.S. government after all.
-Do you have a warrant?
-I do.
I want a lawyer.
I would, too.
You're not free to go,
-Mr. Ealy.
-I want a lawyer.
I don't know who you people are.
Get the fuck out of my way.
Bad call, Richard.
We got a vehicle out back.
We're gonna spare you
the indignity for now.
You haven't read me my rights.
Let me show you my other badge.
You don't have any rights
with this badge.
Why are we even messing
with this guy, anyway?
Could've had CED pick him up,
bring him right to us.
'Cause this guy...
If this guy lived
in a shitty apartment
and donated his entire salary
to the communist party,
I could at least respect
his commitment to the cause.
This asshole lives better
than we do,
then advocates tearing down the
system that allows him to do it.
Nah, fuck him.
I want to look him in the eye
when his fucking world crumbles.
Perks of this job are endless,
ain't they, boss?
Yeah.
Hi.
Hey.
Sure.
Thank you.
Here you go, my love.
How was your day?
I saw a 16-year-old girl
with stage 3 colon cancer.
-In a teenager?
-Yeah.
I didn't think
that was possible.
Yeah, it's becoming
more and more common.
It's got to be
something environmental.
Microplastics
or some preservative
or, you know, something
with greed at its root.
That's pretty deep, babe.
Pretty philosophical
for a physician.
Yeah.
Maybe so, but still true.
I'd ask you
about your day, but...
You can ask.
How was your day?
It was...
illuminating.
Illuminating? How so?
Every enemy we have
has been waging
a 50-year covert war against us,
attacking us
with the tiniest of cuts.
What kind of cuts?
To our infrastructure,
our government, our schools,
social media, everything.
I'm not really following.
How'd they do that?
Lenin used to call
compassionate progressives
in the West "useful idiots"
because, on the surface,
what they wanted
appeared to be what he wanted,
and he used that.
That's how he took power.
And now, they're all doing it,
and they've been doing it
for so long.
Like spies?
Influencers,
information peddlers,
an-an army of useful idiots
for 50 years.
And now,
we're infested with them.
Open mouth.
Come on.